{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which%20of%20these%20levels%20does%20NOT%20appear%20in%20the%20console%2FPC%20versions%20of%20the%20game%20%22Sonic%20Generations%22%3F","correct_answer":"Mushroom%20Hill","incorrect_answers":["City%20Escape","Planet%20Wisp","Sky%20Sanctuary"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Melty%20Blood%20Actress%20Again%20Current%20Code%22%2C%20you%20can%20enter%20Blood%20Heat%20mode%20in%20Half%20Moon%20style.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20what%20prison%20was%20Adolf%20Hitler%20held%20in%201924%3F","correct_answer":"Landsberg%20Prison","incorrect_answers":["Spandau%20Prison","Ebrach%20Abbey","Hohenasperg"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"The%20Swedish%20word%20%22Grunka%22%20means%20what%20in%20English%3F","correct_answer":"Thing","incorrect_answers":["People","Place","Pineapple"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Ellen%20McLain%2C%20the%20voice%20of%20GLaDOS%20in%20the%20Portal%20game%20series%2C%20is%20married%20to%20the%20voice%20actor%20for%20which%20Team%20Fortress%202%20character%3F","correct_answer":"Sniper","incorrect_answers":["Heavy","Soldier","Scout"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"This%20mobile%20OS%20held%20the%20largest%20market%20share%20in%202012.","correct_answer":"iOS","incorrect_answers":["Android","BlackBerry","Symbian"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20%22JoJo%27s%20Bizarre%20Adventure%22%2C%20which%20of%20the%20following%20Stands%20does%20NOT%20have%20a%20time-based%20ability%3F","correct_answer":"20th%20Century%20Boy","incorrect_answers":["Made%20in%20Heaven","Star%20Platinum","The%20World"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who%20voices%20the%20character%20%22Reigen%22%20%20in%20the%20English%20dub%20of%20%22Mob%20Psycho%20100%22%3F","correct_answer":"Chris%20Niosi","incorrect_answers":["Max%20Mittelman","Kyle%20McCarley","Casey%20Mongillo"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which%20ocean%20borders%20the%20west%20coast%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"Pacific","incorrect_answers":["Atlantic","Indian","Arctic"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"On%20the%20periodic%20table%20of%20elements%2C%20what%20is%20the%20symbol%20for%20Tin%3F","correct_answer":"Sn","incorrect_answers":["Ti","Ni","Na"]}]}